http://www.bluecrabbay.com/privacy.asp

Privacy Policy - Our Commitment to Privacy
This notice covers the online information practices of Blue Crab Bay Co.
Blue Crab Bay Co. appreciates the importance of your privacy and the security of your personal data. We have instituted measures to ensure that your personal information is safeguarded. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used.
Information We Collect
When you visit our web site, there are certain places where we ask you to provide us information about you that will enhance your site visit or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate. Places where we request information may include when you place an order, send us email requesting information, or respond to a promotional offer. In such cases, your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, credit card number and expiration date, as well as, personal preference information that is needed to fill your order, register or subscribe you to offers, or make product recommendations, may be requested.
Use of Information
Information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, customer number, and credit card information are used to ship and bill orders. If there is a problem with your order your phone number and email address may be used by customer service to resolve the issue. Preference information may allow our website to make product recommendations to you. In any case, be assured that all employees of Blue Crab Bay Co. are bound by these privacy and security policies.
Opt-in/Opt-out
Persons who communicate with us and therefore supply Blue Crab Bay Co. with an e-mail address may receive future communications from us by e-mail. You can unsubscribe at any time by e-mailing your request to sales@bluecrabbay.com. Simply state, "Do not email" in the body of the message, or by “unclicking” the receive mail on the customer information page. Please allow up to 24 hours for your request to be processed.
Third Party Links
While visiting our site you may be directed to third party sites via links. Blue Crab Bay Co. has no responsibility or liability for these independent parties or their actions, as these outside parties operate under their own privacy and security policies.
Data Security
Blue Crab Bay Co. is committed to the security of information collected on our sites. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Private account information is located behind a firewall; it is not directly connected to the Internet. Information behind the firewall on the customer server is not available to unauthorized computers. The firewall is a recognized industry standard.
Encryption
All data sent to Blue Crab Bay Co. via the Internet is encrypted. Using sophisticated software, any personal information you send to us is scrambled, thus should it be intercepted on route, it is very difficult to decrypt. Only once it is within our firewall will the information be decoded and processed. At Blue Crab Bay Co. we will periodically update our systems to provide you with the most up-to-date security regarding your personal information. As a consequence, our policies may be revised so please review this site periodically for any changes or updates.
How to Contact Us
For additional information about our privacy policy and information maintained about you, please contact us at the following addresses. In any communication, be sure to include your name and mailing address.
E-mail: sales@bluecrabbay.com ~ Mail: Blue Crab Bay Co., 29368 Atlantic Drive, Melfa VA 23410
ï¿½ Copyright 2010 All Rights Reserved, Blue Crab Bay Co. is a Registered Trademark
